who is to blame for the fact that the Russians are killing people in Ukraine
кто виноват в том что в Украине убивают
and why do you communicate here, we just
людей а чём общаетесь тут просто
communicate with people, I understand, but
общаемся с людьми понял а Украину
you specifically choose Ukraine, we didn’t put it on
специально выбираете не мы поставили на
Random, I understood And whose
Рандом понял А чей
Crimea we don’t
Крым мы не
know. Well, if you look at the map now, then
знаем Ну если смотреть сейчас по карте
why not yet? Well, we don’t  we know
то пока что почему пока Ну мы не знаем
we don’t know we don’t know
мы не знаем мы не знаем
In short, I understand you’re braver than even your
Короче я понял ты смелее даже своего
boyfriend
парня
Yes,
Да
who is this my
кто это моя
sister In short, you’re really braver than your brother At
сестра Короче ты реально смелее брата Ты
least you’re not afraid to formulate your thoughts somehow
хоть не боишься свою мысль как-то
So I said, I don’t know Well,
сформулировать Так я же сказал я не знаю
yes, but you tell her the
Ну да но ты ей говори
sign It happens  It’s okay, you
знаку Бывает такое Ничего страшного ты
were born this way, born with a kun, you understand,
родился родился с куном понимаешь ну
well, you can’t change yourself,
себя же не изменишь
like, well, you can change, you can develop and
типа ну можно менять можно развиваться и
change yourself. What questions do you have for me?
менять себя А у вас какие вопросы ко мне
No, just how are you doing? How are you in the
никакие просто Как дела у вас Как
mood, that is, your country is
настроение то есть ваша страна
firing missiles at my country and you?
обстреливает ракетами мою страну и вы
you ask how I’m in a
спрашиваете как у меня
good mood. Maybe you’re in a good
настроение Вдруг у вас хорошее
mood, we’re in a good mood,
настроение у нас же хорошее настроение
Nope, because you’re shelling, you’re
Нуне потому что вы обстреливает вы
not killing people. Well, it’s not us that’s
убиваете людей не мы Ну это же не мы
firing specifically. I do
обстреливать конкретно А
n’t know who, probably the military. We’re good.
кто не знаю наверное военные Мы хорошо А
Who’s to blame for the fact that they’re killing in Ukraine?
кто кто виноват в том что в Украине
Russians
убивают россияне
people Well, sometimes there are warriors, no one is to
людей Ну бывает воины бывают не кто кто
blame, there was a war, I don’t know, no one is to
виноват были была война не знаю никто не
blame Just like no one is [ __ ] if
виноват Просто как никто не сри если
someone took a knife and stabbed someone Well, who is to
кто-то взял нож и кого-то зарезал Ну кто
blame, they don’t say no one is to blame, they are
виноват не говорят никто не виноват
both to blame among themselves Poly government
виноваты оба между собой Поли
government quarreled
правительство правительство поссорилась
among themselves and it happened what
между собой а и получилось что
happened Well, don’t wait, what
получилось Ну а не подожди что
happened who attacked whom turned out there is
получилось кто на кого напал
no data again, look
получилось данных нет ещё раз смотри
if for example your neighbor is now breaking into your apartment
если например вам в квартиру сейчас
and starts shooting at you,
заломи Сосед и начнёт в вас стрелять
both are to blame or there is no one to blame, somehow we
обое или виноватых нет чем-то мы им
pleased them and what can be done  once again why it is necessary
угодили а чем можно ещё раз чем это надо
not to please so that it is normal that you are to
не угодить чтобы было нормально что вы
blame the same as that he ran in you He
виноваты то же что вас Он застрелил
shot him Well, we wanted it like that And what is your
забежал Ну захотелось мы так так А ваша
fault,
вина в
look, a drunk neighbor runs in with
чём вот смотри забегает пьяный сосед с
a gun Yes, your brother has
пистолетом Да твоему брату засовывают
mops shoved right up to his tonsils Yes And you are short
швабры по самое гланды Да А тебя короче
there  zhart is fried in short then they also
там жарт жарят короче потом ещё типа
mate your stomach and pierce your brains
тебе спаривают живот пробивают мозги
In short, yes, it’s your fault for this
Короче да ты виновата в этом
Well, you’re somehow comparing different things Well,
Ну вы как-то разные вещи сравниваете Ну
they’re different Just like different, simple What’s the
это же разные Совсем как разные просто В
point
чём суть
And now you’re saying that it’s our
А вы сейчас говорите что это мы
fault specifically We We’re different people
виноваты конкретно Мы Мы же разные люди
everything is correct, there are people who
все правильно есть люди которые
support all this And there are people who,
поддерживают это всё А есть люди которые
well, have a neutral attitude towards this or
Ну нейтрально к этому относятся или
in general Look, I didn’t ask now or are you
вообще Смотри я сейчас не спросил или ты
to blame, I asked who is
виновата я спросил кто
to blame Who is to blame for the
виноват Кто виноват что напали на
government attacking Ukraine
Украину правительство
What is common to the fact that they could not
Какое общее тем что не смогли
agree What is common What is common
договориться Какое общее Что за общее
government of
правительство
some kind of reptilians Freemasons Who where where is
какое-то рептилоиды масоны Кто где где
this government the name of the person
это правительство фамилию человека
who heads this government
который это правительство
what well Who heads this
возглавляет что ну Кто возглавляет это
government Biden there
правительство байден там
sizen Ignatius Lala
сизен Игнатий Лала
who I don’t
кто я не
know Why I don’t want to answer what
знаю Зачем Я не хочу отвечать на какие
question I am this
вопрос я находится это
government Where is this
правительство Где находится это
government that is to blame  that she
правительство которое виновата что она
attacked what And which one are you talking about?
напала что А вы про какое именно правите
Well, which attacked you say which is to
Ну которая напала вы говорите которая
blame? It’s you, well, you say that some
виновата Это же вы ну вы вы говорите что
government is to blame. Which is
виновато какое-то правительство
not us, it said it’s to blame? Which who
Какое не мы оно сказа винова Какие кто
attacked, wait, that is, you are now
напали подожди то есть ты сейчас
saying that the government is to blame?
говоришь что виновато правительство
Which attacked?  and the government
Какое напало и виновато правительство на
that was
какое
attacked is to blame Well, name these two governments
напали А ну назви эти два правительства
who attacked and which one was
кто напал и На какое
attacked There is no information about who attacked whom Damn the
напали Нет данных кто на кого напал Блин
guy’s [ __ ] is shrinking right now It’s just
у пацана сейчас очко сжимается Просто
unrealistic Did you look or something And
короче нереально А ты ь смотрел что ли А
your eyes are so
так у тебя глаза короче аж такие
frightened in short She’s at least  He opens his mouth and isn’t
перепуганные Она хоть рот открывает не
afraid to say. You’re just crap. Well,
боится сказать А ты просто обосра Ну так
tell me, mom’s here, that’s
скажи мамка пришла
it.
всё